So we're looking for this apartment.
所以我们正在寻找这间公寓。
We see the post we call the phone number within the listing within the post and somebody picks up and
我们看到我们在帖子中的列表中拨打电话号码的帖子，有人接听并
says hello.
打招呼。
Well the first thing you need to do is confirm that this is the right person.
那么你需要做的第一件事就是确认这是对的人。
Right.
正确的。
So you might start by saying yes is is this the owner of.
所以你可能会先说是的，这是它的所有者。
Is this the owner of the or is this the landlord.
这是楼主还是楼主。
You could also say landlord of the apartment in Greenpoint.
您也可以说是 Greenpoint 公寓的房东。
That's listed on Zillow.
这在 Zillow 上列出。
Dot com.
点com。
Or you could say I'm calling about the.
或者你可以说我在打电话。
And then you can say what you're calling about.
然后你就可以说出你在说什么。
I'm calling about the one bedroom apartment in Greenpoint.
我正在打电话询问Greenpoint的一居室公寓。
That's on Zillow dot com.
那是在 Zillow dot com 上。
Is this the.
这是吗。
Is this the owner.
这是楼主吗。
You could say the newly renovated one bedroom Greenpoint apartment.
你可以说是新装修的一居室Greenpoint公寓。
Hello.
你好。
I'm calling about the renovated one bedroom apartment in Greenpoint.
我正在打电话询问Greenpoint 翻新的一居室公寓。
That's posted on Zillow dot com.
这是在 Zillow dot com 上发布的。
Is this the owner not Are you the owner.
这是所有者 不是您是所有者。
If we're on the phone we should say is this the owner.
如果我们在打电话，我们应该说这是所有者。
OK this is when you say your own name.
好的，这是当你说出你自己的名字的时候。
And is this when you're on the phone.
这是当你打电话的时候。
This is how we say it basically.
我们基本上是这样说的。
We usually don't say I am I am OK.
我们通常不会说我很好，我很好。
Yes this is the owner.
是的，这就是主人。
Yes.
是的。
This is the owner.
这是主人。
OK great.
好，很好。
Well I'm just wondering first.
好吧，我只是想先。
That's the first thing I want to say.
这是我要说的第一件事。
If the apartment is still available because I'm very interested in taking a look at it.
如果公寓仍然可用，因为我非常有兴趣看看它。
If so if we use if so when we want to say if this thing is true.
If so if 当我们想说这件事是否真实时，我们使用 if so。
Right.
正确的。
You look tired.
你看起来很累。
Are you tired.
你累了吗。
If so you should take a nap if so if you're tired it's a way to say if this thing is true and it's pretty
如果是这样，你应该小睡一下
common actually now it's important not to say I really really really want to live here.
其实现在很常见，重要的是不要说我真的真的很想住在这里。
I want to rent this apartment because then later you can't talk about the price probably.
我想租这间公寓，因为以后你可能不能谈论价格。
Maybe it will be harder for you to negotiate.
也许你会更难谈判。
Which means to get maybe get a better price so it's better to just say that you're interested in the
这意味着可能会得到更好的价格，所以最好只是说你对
apartment.
公寓。
OK great.
好，很好。
I'm just wondering if just wondering if the apartment is still available because I'm very interested
我只是想知道是否只是想知道公寓是否仍然可用，因为我很感兴趣
in taking a look.
在看一看。
If so we're taking a look at it.
如果是这样，我们正在研究它。
If so a few people have come by for showings but it's still available.
如果是这样的话，有几个人来观看，但它仍然可用。
So if somebody comes by that means you go to a place for a short time.
因此，如果有人经过那意味着您会去一个地方很短的时间。
My friend came by yesterday and we talked for an hour or I'm going to stop by the bookstore for a few
我的朋友昨天来了，我们聊了一个小时，或者我要去书店停下来几个
minutes before I go home.
在我回家前几分钟。
We often use come by stopped by and we talk about going to a place usually for a short period of time
我们经常用 come by stop by 和我们谈论去一个地方通常很短的时间
for showings showings.
为看房看房。
It's when you actually show an apartment to somebody who might live there but it's still available.
当您实际向可能住在那里但仍然可用的人展示公寓时。
So people saw it but they haven't yet decided to rent the place.
所以人们看到了，但他们还没有决定租这个地方。
OK so maybe that gives me a feeling of pressure.
好吧，也许这让我有压力感。
Maybe I need to hurry up a little bit.
也许我需要快一点。
OK that's great.
太棒了。
That means it's still available.
这意味着它仍然可用。
So the first thing you should do when you call is make sure that from the time that you saw or the time
所以当你打电话时你应该做的第一件事是确保从你看到的时间或时间
that the listing was posted and the time you're calling from that time to this time nobody has actually
该列表已发布，并且从那时到现在您打电话的时间没有人有实际上
rented the apartment.
租了公寓。
You need to make sure about that first.
你需要先确定这一点。
Usually that's the first thing.
通常这是第一件事。
Then you can get into some of the details.
然后你可以进入一些细节。
OK that's great.
太棒了。
Do you think I could ask a few questions.
你觉得我可以问几个问题。
Could I ask a few questions.
我能问几个问题吗？
I'd like to ask a few questions.
我想问几个问题。
Do you think I could ask a few questions is really really polite.
你觉得我能问几个问题真的很客气。
Maybe it's too polite.
可能是太客气了。
Maybe it's very polite.
也许这是非常礼貌的。
You can also.
你也可以。
It's just fine to say I'd like to ask a few questions or can I ask a couple questions.
可以说我想问几个问题，或者我可以问几个问题。
I'd like to to ask a few questions then they might say go ahead go ahead go ahead.
我想问几个问题，然后他们可能会说去吧去吧去吧。
That means please do.
这意味着请做。
Please do.
请做。
If we ask a question do you think I could ask a few questions.
如果我们问一个问题，你认为我可以问几个问题。
Yeah absolutely.
是的，绝对的。
Or maybe.
或者可能。
Sure.
当然。
Or.
或者。
Okay.
好的。
And then that means you need to say what your questions are.
然后这意味着你需要说出你的问题是什么。
Well I'd like to know more about the neighborhood.
好吧，我想了解更多关于附近的信息。
I'd like to know more about the neighborhood and also whether or not pets are allowed.
我想了解更多关于附近以及是否允许携带宠物的信息。
I have a cat.
我有一只猫。 现在请注意，这实际上不是一个问题，但它有点像一个问题，即使它没有被说成是一个问题
question because you are making an inquiry or an inquiry.
提问，因为您正在进行询问或询问。
You're getting more information.
你得到更多的信息。
We could easily say this as a question do you think you could tell me.
我们可以很容易地说这是一个问题，你认为你可以告诉我。
Or could you tell me if the neighborhood is safe or not.
或者你能告诉我附近是否安全。
Or could you tell me a little bit about the neighborhood.
或者你能告诉我一些关于附近的事情吗？
And also do you allow cats in the apartment.
你也允许猫在公寓里吗？
Are are cats allowed our cats allowed.
是否允许猫允许我们的猫允许。
I have one.
我有一个。
I have one so it's still kind of a question even though it isn't really a question because it doesn't
我有一个，所以它仍然是一个问题，即使它不是一个真正的问题，因为它不是
have a question mark but we could very easily ask this as a question.
有一个问号，但我们可以很容易地问这个问题。
We would just use some of the phrases that we learned at the very beginning of this lesson.
我们将只使用我们在本课开始时学到的一些短语。
So now we have our answer from the landlord.
所以现在我们从房东那里得到了答案。
As for the neighborhood.
至于小区。
As for the neighborhood when we use as for something as for you.
什么东西使用时候的附近你。
Well as for the report you wrote yesterday means this is the topic I'm going to talk about.
至于你昨天写的报告，这就是我要谈的话题。
As for the neighborhood it's relatively quiet.
至于小区，还是比较安静的。
It's pretty quiet.
它很安静。
It's it's kind of quiet ok which is a good thing usually but there are a lot of great places to eat
它有点安静，这通常是一件好事，但有很多好吃的地方
nearby.
附近。
Why would the landlord say.
楼主为什么要说。
But he could say and I guess.
但他可以说，我猜。
But maybe that landlord is thinking a quiet place.
但也许那个房东正在考虑一个安静的地方。
Maybe suggests that it's not very interesting and there aren't a lot of things to do.
也许暗示这不是很有趣，也没有很多事情要做。
I'm saying it's quiet it's peaceful and at the same time there are lots of things to do.
我是说这里很安静，很平静，同时还有很多事情要做。
Lots of places to eat but there are lots of great places to eat nearby.
吃饭的地方很多，但附近有很多好吃的地方。
The school is within walking distance walking distance is kind of a subjective word that means maybe
学校在步行距离之内步行距离是一种主观的词，这意味着也许
different people have a different idea about what that means but we can say it's probably less than
不同的人对这意味着什么有不同的想法，但我们可以说它可能小于
10 minutes.
10分钟。
And the subway is just a five minute walk away a five minute walk here.
地铁距离这里只有五分钟的步行路程。
It's quite interesting we can make our own adjectives a five minute walk thirty two page book The short
很有趣，我们可以自己造形容词 五分钟步行 32 页的书 短
book a three hour bus ride a 15 year old maybe a 15 year old movie.
预订一个 15 岁或 15 岁的电影的三个小时的巴士车程。
OK so we can make our own adjectives by adding a hyphen ups a hyphen hyphen is this one that goes between
好的，所以我们可以通过添加 hy 来制作自己的形容词phen ups a hyphen hyphen 是介于两者之间的那个
the number and the noun.
数字和名词。
Take away the S and then it makes an adjective.
去掉 S，然后它变成一个形容词。
So it's a five minute walk away.
所以步行五分钟就到了。
Albert Park is a made up park name is right across the street right.
阿尔伯特公园是一个虚构的公园名称就在街对面。
Gives us a feeling of it being very close right across the street doesn't mean this right doesn't mean
让我们感觉它就在街对面很近并不意味着这个权利并不意味着
that right.
没错。
It just means directly.
就是直接的意思。
So it's a great location and totally safe.
所以这是一个很棒的位置而且完全安全。
Oh so I've just remembered your other question.
哦，所以我才想起你的另一个问题。
Your other thing was about if your cat is allowed right.
你的另一件事是关于你的猫是否被允许。
Oh and cats are allowed but no big dogs no big dogs no big dogs allowed.
哦，猫是允许的，但不允许大狗没有大狗不允许大狗。
So when you remember something you go Oh yeah.
所以，当你记得某事时，你会去哦，是的。
And about cats.
关于猫。
As for cats.
至于猫。
As for your cat we use as for when we want to mention a topic.
至于你的猫，我们在想提及话题的时候使用。
So the landlord has answered my initial inquiries about whether or not the apartment is available.
所以房东已经回答了我关于公寓是否可用的初步询问。
About whether or not I can bring my cats and about the neighborhood.
关于我是否可以带我的猫和关于附近的事情。
The landlord has told me about how nice the neighborhood is.
房东告诉我附近有多好。
But I still have a few more things I'd like to know once we get into the conversation a little bit.
但是，一旦我们开始对话，我还有一些想知道的事情。
Then we can start using more direct language.
然后我们可以开始使用更直接的语言。
If you use too many of the polite phrases that we learned at the beginning of the lesson then sometimes
如果你使用了太多我们在课程开始时学到的礼貌用语，那么有时
the conversation won't flow so it's okay.
谈话不会进行，所以没关系。
Once you get into it to start using some more direct questions.
一旦你进入它开始使用一些更直接的问题。
Now I'm going to get a little bit more information and we're gonna start talking about the rent and
现在我要获得更多信息 我们要开始谈论租金和
when we talk about the rent we need to do a little bit of negotiation.
当我们谈论租金时，我们需要进行一些谈判。
So to negotiate means to discuss price.
因此，谈判意味着讨论价格。
Often you can negotiate about lots of different things but often in America when you negotiate you need
通常你可以就很多不同的事情进行谈判，但通常在美国，当你谈判时你需要
to give up something so that you can get something you need to make an offer.
放弃一些东西，这样你就可以得到你需要的东西来提出要约。
You need to make an offer.
你需要出价。
Rarely in America do people just say can you give me a lower price.
在美国很少有人会说你能给我一个更低的价格。
Can you please give me a discount.
你能给我打折吗？
There has to be a reason.
一定是有原因的。
So we'll look at that.
所以我们会看看那个。
We'll look at that in the rest of this inquiry situation.
我们将在剩下的调查情况中研究这一点。
That's great.
那太棒了。
Thank you for the information and about the rent.
感谢您提供有关租金的信息。
So now I'm changing topics to talk about.
所以现在我要换个话题来谈谈。
Talk about money how much I will need to pay.
谈钱我需要付多少钱。
OK.
好的。
Are the utilities included are the utilities included so utilities are the things you need to pay that
是否包含公用事业是包含的公用事业，因此公用事业是您需要支付的费用
your apartment runs on so electricity may maybe gas water Internet.
你的公寓运行，所以电可能是煤气水互联网。
These things are utilities if they're included that means you don't need to pay any extra if the rent
这些东西是公用事业，如果它们包括在内，这意味着如果租金你不需要支付任何额外费用
is one thousand five hundred dollars or fifteen hundred dollars.
是一千五百美元或一千五百美元。
I don't need to pay more than one thousand five hundred.
我不需要支付超过一千五百。
They're part of that.
他们是其中的一部分。
Heating and water are included.
包括暖气和水。
This is pretty common.
这很常见。
Heating and water are included but electricity and Wi-Fi are not.
包括暖气和水，但不包括电和 Wi-Fi。
So that means you don't need to worry about heating and water but you do need to pay for the electricity.
所以这意味着你不需要担心暖气和水，但你需要支付电费。
Depending on how much you use and of course Wi-Fi you would have to pay for those yourself.
根据您使用的数量，当然还有 Wi-Fi，您必须自己支付这些费用。
OK.
好的。
No problem.
没问题。
Now we get into the negotiation one thousand five hundred is a little over my budget over my budget.
现在我们开始谈判一千五百是我的预算超过我的预算。
OK over my budget means it's more than I really want to to spend it's more than I planned to spend.
好的，超出我的预算意味着它比我真正想要的要多，比我计划的要多。
We can also say out of my price range that out of my price range a bit over my budget.
我们也可以说超出我的价格范围超出了我的预算。
OK so we're sort of expressing a bit of pain.
好的，所以我们表达了一点痛苦。
This is common in an English negotiation.
这在英语谈判中很常见。
First you say oh I don't know I can't.
首先你说哦我不知道我不能。
And then OK.
然后确定。
And it looks a little high for the area as well.
而且该地区看起来也有点高。
So that means in this neighborhood maybe I saw some other apartments that were cheaper or maybe I saw
所以这意味着在这个街区也许我看到了其他一些更便宜的公寓，或者我看到了
one that was a little bigger and it was the same price.
一个大一点的，价格一样。
I think it's too expensive.
我觉得太贵了。
This high means too expensive a little high for the area as well.
这个高也意味着该地区太贵了。
So I'm sort of trying to get to some point I'm trying to say can you give me a lower rent but I don't
所以我有点想达到某个点我想说你能不能给我一个更低的租金但我不
want to just say can you give me a lower rent.
我只想说你能不能给我一个更低的租金。
Would you consider one thousand three hundred if I sign a two year lease so a lease is a rental contract
如果我签两年的租约，你会考虑一千三百吗？所以租约是租赁合同
when you rent an apartment.
当你租公寓时。
We call it off in America we call it a lease.
在美国，我们称之为租约。
We say Would you consider when we want to offer something when we want to offer maybe what we will do.
我们说，当我们想提供某些东西时，您会考虑我们会做什么。
And we are suggesting that we pay a little bit less.
我们建议我们少付一点钱。
Would you consider thirteen hundred if I sign a two year lease if I signed a two year lease.
如果我签了两年的租约，你会考虑一千三百吗？
Then you don't have to worry about finding another person to live in this apartment.
这样您就不必担心找不到另一个人住在这间公寓里。
Another tenant tenant is a person who lives in usually in an apartment.
另一个租户租户是通常住在公寓里的人。
My tenants my tenants the people who live in my in the houses I own or the apartments I own.
我的租户 我的租户 住在我拥有的房屋或公寓中的人。
So would you consider it's really common.
所以你会认为它真的很常见。
But the landlord doesn't really want to talk about it on the phone.
不过楼主实在不想在电话里说。
The landlord wants to show the apartment first and then talk about price stuff.
房东想先介绍一下公寓，然后再谈价格。
We could talk about that once you've come by for a look.
一旦你过来看看，我们可以谈谈。
So the landlord is putting it off put it off.
所以楼主拖拖拉拉。
That means to push that back for for a later discussion.
这意味着将其推回以供以后讨论。
Maybe I might be willing to be flexible on that.
也许我可能愿意在这方面保持灵活。
I might be willing to be flexible on that.
我可能愿意在这方面保持灵活。
I know that sounds a little bit weird but flexible means that my my position on something or what I
我知道这听起来有点奇怪但灵活意味着我对某事或我的立场
think about something might change a little bit.
想想有些事情可能会改变一点。
We can negotiate more.
我们可以协商更多。
I'm really trying to get you to come to look at the place to look at the apartment and then we can negotiate
我真的想让你来看看那个地方看看公寓然后我们可以谈判
about the rent.
关于租金。
About the the price right.
关于价格合适。
So I'm okay with the idea of talking about it later.
所以我同意稍后再谈的想法。
When do you think I could stop by.
你觉得我什么时候可以过来。
And this is pretty polite.
这是非常有礼貌的。
Would tomorrow afternoon work.
明天下午上班。
Remember from our class our lesson about inviting.
记住我们班上关于邀请的课程。
We use work in this way to suggest a time.
我们以这种方式使用工作来建议时间。
Does that time work for you.
那个时间对你有用吗。
Would tomorrow afternoon work for you.
明天下午会为你工作。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah that would be perfect.
是的，那将是完美的。
That would be perfect would be perfect.
那将是完美的将是完美的。
3 pm now you could say is 3 p.m. okay.
下午 3 点现在你可以说是下午 3 点。好的。
Is 3 p.m. OK but to make it shorter sometimes we'll just say 3 p.m. 3 p.m. or 5 p.m. 4 p.m. whatever.
是下午 3 点好的，但有时为了缩短时间，我们会说下午 3 点。下午 3 点或下午 5 点下午4点。任何。
Great right.
太好了。
Could you text me the address text here is a verb that means give me exactly where I need to go.
你能给我发短信吗，这里的地址文本是一个动词，意思是告诉我我需要去的地方。
Send it to me in a message to this number maybe.
或许可以通过消息发送给我这个号码。
Could you text me the address.
你能把地址发短信给我吗？
Yes.
是的。
See you tomorrow.
明天见。
So this is a very common very normal situation.
所以这是很常见很正常的情况。
This kind of thing happens all the time.
这种事情一直在发生。
And if you find yourself in a situation where you need to ask for information.
如果您发现自己处于需要询问信息的情况。
Remember start with some of the phrases that we learned early on at the beginning of the lesson and
记住从我们在课程开始时学过的一些短语开始，然后
then once you get into the discussion into the conversation don't worry too much about using them.
那么一旦你进入讨论，就不要太担心使用它们。
You can ask direct questions like are the blah blah blah blah blah.
你可以问直接的问题，比如等等等等。
Does the apartment have furniture.
公寓有家具吗。
Does the electricity work it's OK to use those questions.
用电可以用这些问题。
Once you get in it and then maybe when you're going to say goodbye then you can start using some more
一旦你进入它，然后也许当你要说再见时，你就可以开始使用更多
polite language again like when do you think I could stop by.
再次礼貌的语言，比如你认为我什么时候可以停下来。
Right.
正确的。
That's very polite very very respectful beginning an end pretty polite pretty respectful the middle
非常有礼貌 非常有礼貌 开始 结束 非常有礼貌 非常有礼貌 中间
just go through the details and ask what you want to ask.
只需浏览详细信息并询问您想问什么。